socialmediasun.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Social Media Sun

**The title of this web site is Social Media Sun™ and we have as our principal activity the transmission of Articles written by several authors, and offering networking solutions for social media users or bloggers. We may also engage in other activities as we see fit.**

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email, by subscribing to our blog, signing up for our various tools or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to the Feedburner app to send your subscription content. We request information from you on our contact form. To receive a reply, you must provide contact information (like name and e-mail address). This information will only be used to contact you in regards to your specified inquiry. We ask for certain identifiable information on our Best Blogs list. This information is only used to create your account and correspond with you in regards to the actions you need to take to make use of the application.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**COPPA Statement**

We do not collect nor maintain personally identifiable information from individual users under the age of thirteen (13) years under any circumstances.

The privacy and thus the safety of young persons is of the utmost importance. Personal information is defined as individually identifiable information such as an e-mail address, a telephone number, first and last name, a home or other physical address including a street name, city or town and the like. We are committed to respecting and protecting your personal privacy paying particular attention to the privacy needs of children. While the content of this site is directed at an older demographic, I have taken care to exclude any material that would be considered inappropriate for a younger audience. Children under the age of thirteen (13) should not interact with the contact page, or any commenting features on this site. In the instance a child does convey personal information that is considered identifiable, we have pledged to report it to authorities with the goal of having them notify the parents. Any user who indicates they are under the age of thirteen (13) will be banned from interactive content until their parents contact administrators directly.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or contact form on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Security**  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Any transactions completed online in regards to services rendered are processed through PayPal, that information is encrypted and transmitted in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While PayPal uses encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your personal contact information both online and offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, customer service or notifications) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately through our contact form.**
